I was standing in the quiet watching shadows softly breathe
Those unspoken wishes like a mystery
Every step feels bigger than but a crowd is all to me
I don't know who is waiting there but I'll let it be
If I fall, I die before
If I break, let there be light
There's a world behind the fear So it can make me feel alive
Seeing a storm start to avoid
Showing the miracle we made This time we're about to fly
No more fending, drifting by
We keep moving
We keep it when I'm standing still I'm not losing
You and your song we're writing still
Knowing the ending I know I don't need to see the proof
The sign is lightening up
Like he's calling me to you
I remember all the versions
Some are lonely, some are ill or still
No more running away Just hearing echoes afar
If the future is a puzzle
I am brave enough to solve it If the end is just a journey
I'll be ready for the call
If I fall, I can be far
If I break, let there be light There's a world behind the fear
So it can make me feel alive
We keep moving
We keep it when I'm standing still I'm not losing
You left me somewhere right still Knowing the ending
I know I don't need to see it through
I'm silent right now He's calling me to you
I can feel it pushing on me Up when the sky, he falls on top of me
I don't look back, I only take the ugly for a new one now
We keep moving
We keep it wet and I'm standing still I'm not losing you, I'm somewhere
right still Knowing the ending,
I know I don't need to see it through I'm signing this line up, signing this line up
He's calling me to you